newhealthtoday.net 2016-11-12

# Privacy Policy

Protecting your privacy is very important to us. We’re telling you about our privacy policy so you know what information we collect, why we collect it, and what we do with it. This privacy notice is for Newhealthtoday.net, CuidadoDeSalud.gov, and other Newhealthtoday.net subdomains such as Finder.Newhealthtoday.net. These sites are referred to as “Newhealthtoday.net” throughout the rest of this notice and are maintained and operated by the Centers for Medicare & Medicaid Services (CMS). This privacy notice aligns with the CMS Privacy Policy.

CMS, operating Newhealthtoday.net, does not collect name, contact information, social security number or other similar information unless you choose to provide it. We do collect other limited information automatically from visitors who read, browse, and/or download information from our site. We do this so we can understand how the site is being used and how we can make it more helpful. See the Types of information we collect section below for more information.

Personally identifiable information (PII), defined by the Office of Management and Budget (OMB), refers to information which can be used to distinguish or trace an individual’s identity, such as their name, social security number, biometric records, etc. alone, or when combined with other personal or identifying information which is linked or linkable to a specific individual, such as date and place of birth, mother’s maiden name, etc.

If you create a user account, fill out an application for health care coverage, and use other tools on the site (such as identity verification), CMS collects personally identifiable information. This information is collected in order to provide the services Newhealthtoday.net is designed to offer – to compare health insurance plans based on costs, benefits, and other important features; to determine eligibility for health coverage and cost-sharing reductions; to choose a plan; and to enroll in coverage.

CMS does not sell any information entered into Newhealthtoday.net. For information on how we share information, see How CMS uses information collected using Newhealthtoday.net.
